{
    "subject": "Tom_Hanks",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Rita_Wilson",
    "human_readable": "Tom Hanks is married to Rita Wilson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9884485602378845,
            "question": "Is Rita Wilson married to Tom Hanks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9860361814498901,
            "question": "Are Tom Hanks and Rita Wilson married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8675761222839355,
            "question": "To whom is Tom Hanks married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.856928825378418,
            "question": "Who is Tom Hanks married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7627896070480347,
            "question": "Who are the spouses of Tom Hanks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7597763538360596,
            "question": "Does Tom Hanks have a spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6520782113075256,
            "question": "Who is Rita Wilson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5983381867408752,
            "question": "What is the name of Tom Hanks's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5952901244163513,
            "question": "Is Tom Hanks in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5796399712562561,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Tom Hanks?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tom Hanks is married to Rita Wilson.",
            "html": "yago_968_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Tom Hanks in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_968_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Tom Hanks's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_968_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Rita Wilson?",
            "html": "yago_968_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_968_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_968_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_968_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_968_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_968_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_968_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_968_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_968_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_968_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_968_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple \"Tom Hanks is married to Rita Wilson\".\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nReasoning:\n\n* Multiple documents mention that Tom Hanks and Rita Wilson met on the set of Bosom Buddies in 1981.\n* Documents also state that they got married in 1988, and are celebrating their 35-year anniversary (or have been married for over 30 years).\n* There is no information to suggest that Tom Hanks has ever been married to someone else after Rita Wilson. In fact, the documents imply that he was still married to his first wife when he met Rita.\n* The documents consistently refer to Rita Wilson as Tom Hanks' wife, further supporting this triple.\n\nTherefore, based on the context information provided, it appears that the statement \"Tom Hanks is married to Rita Wilson\" is indeed supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Tom Hanks has been married to Rita Wilson since 1988, with their marriage lasting over 30 years. The information provided supports the statement that Tom Hanks is married to Rita Wilson."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}